http://newyorkrangerscafe.com/index.php?privacy-policy/

New York Rangers Café
1. An overview of data protection
GeneralThe following gives a simple overview of what happens to your personal information when you visit our website. Personal information is any data with which you could be personally identified. Detailed information on the subject of data protection can be found in our privacy policy found below.Data collection on our websiteWho is responsible for the data collection on this website?The data collected on this website are processed by the website operator. The operator's contact details can be found in the website's required legal notice.How do we collect your data?Some data are collected when you provide it to us. This could, for example, be data you enter on a contact form.Other data are collected automatically by our IT systems when you visit the website. These data are primarily technical data such as the browser and operating system you are using or when you accessed the page. These data are collected automatically as soon as you enter our website.What do we use your data for?Part of the data is collected to ensure the proper functioning of the website. Other data can be used to analyze how visitors use the site.What rights do you have regarding your data?You always have the right to request information about your stored data, its origin, its recipients, and the purpose of its collection at no charge. You also have the right to request that it be corrected, blocked, or deleted. You can contact us at any time using the address given in the legal notice if you have further questions about the issue of privacy and data protection. You may also, of course, file a complaint with the competent regulatory authorities.2. General information and mandatory information
Data protectionThe operators of this website take the protection of your personal data very seriously. We treat your personal data as confidential and in accordance with the statutory data protection regulations and this privacy policy.If you use this website, various pieces of personal data will be collected. Personal information is any data with which you could be personally identified. This privacy policy explains what information we collect and what we use it for. It also explains how and for what purpose this happens.Please note that data transmitted via the internet (e.g. via email communication) may be subject to security breaches. Complete protection of your data from third-party access is not possible.Notice concerning the party responsible for this websiteThe party responsible for processing data on this website is:[name and address of the responsible party]Telephone: [telephone number of the responsible party]
Email: [email address of the responsible party]The responsible party is the natural or legal person who alone or jointly with others decides on the purposes and means of processing personal data (names, email addresses, etc.).Revocation of your consent to the processing of your dataMany data processing operations are only possible with your express consent. You may revoke your consent at any time with future effect. An informal email making this request is sufficient. The data processed before we receive your request may still be legally processed.Right to file complaints with regulatory authoritiesIf there has been a breach of data protection legislation, the person affected may file a complaint with the competent regulatory authorities. The competent regulatory authority for matters related to data protection legislation is the data protection officer of the state in which our company is headquartered. A list of data protection officers and their contact details can be found at the following link: https://www.bfdi.bund.de/DE/In…schriften_links-node.html.Right to data portabilityYou have the right to have data which we process based on your consent or in fulfillment of a contract automatically delivered to yourself or to a third party in a standard, machine-readable format. If you require the direct transfer of data to another responsible party, this will only be done to the extent technically feasible.Information, blocking, deletionAs permitted by law, you have the right to be provided at any time with information free of charge about any of your personal data that is stored as well as its origin, the recipient and the purpose for which it has been processed. You also have the right to have this data corrected, blocked or deleted. You can contact us at any time using the address given in our legal notice if you have further questions on the topic of personal data.Opposition to promotional emailsWe hereby expressly prohibit the use of contact data published in the context of website legal notice requirements with regard to sending promotional and informational materials not expressly requested. The website operator reserves the right to take specific legal action if unsolicited advertising material, such as email spam, is received.3. Data collection on our website
CookiesSome of our web pages use cookies. Cookies do not harm your computer and do not contain any viruses. Cookies help make our website more user-friendly, efficient, and secure. Cookies are small text files that are stored on your computer and saved by your browser.Most of the cookies we use are so-called "session cookies." They are automatically deleted after your visit. Other cookies remain in your device's memory until you delete them. These cookies make it possible to recognize your browser when you next visit the site.You can configure your browser to inform you about the use of cookies so that you can decide on a case-by-case basis whether to accept or reject a cookie. Alternatively, your browser can be configured to automatically accept cookies under certain conditions or to always reject them, or to automatically delete cookies when closing your browser. Disabling cookies may limit the functionality of this website.Cookies which are necessary to allow electronic communications or to provide certain functions you wish to use (such as the shopping cart) are stored pursuant to Art. 6 paragraph 1, letter f of GDPR. The website operator has a legitimate interest in the storage of cookies to ensure an optimized service provided free of technical errors. If other cookies (such as those used to analyze your surfing behavior) are also stored, they will be treated separately in this privacy policy.Server log filesThe website provider automatically collects and stores information that your browser automatically transmits to us in "server log files". These are: Browser type and browser version Operating system used Referrer URL Host name of the accessing computer Time of the server request IP address These data will not be combined with data from other sources.The basis for data processing is Art. 6 (1) (b) GDPR, which allows the processing of data to fulfill a contract or for measures preliminary to a contract.Contact formShould you send us questions via the contact form, we will collect the data entered on the form, including the contact details you provide, to answer your question and any follow-up questions. We do not share this information without your permission.We will, therefore, process any data you enter onto the contact form only with your consent per Art. 6 (1)(a) GDPR. You may revoke your consent at any time. An informal email making this request is sufficient. The data processed before we receive your request may still be legally processed.We will retain the data you provide on the contact form until you request its deletion, revoke your consent for its storage, or the purpose for its storage no longer pertains (e.g. after fulfilling your request). Any mandatory statutory provisions, especially those regarding mandatory data retention periods, remain unaffected by this provision.Registration on this websiteYou can register on our website in order to access additional functions offered here. The input data will only be used for the purpose of using the respective site or service for which you have registered. The mandatory information requested during registration must be provided in full. Otherwise, we will reject your registration.To inform you about important changes such as those within the scope of our site or technical changes, we will use the email address specified during registration.We will process the data provided during registration only based on your consent per Art. 6 (1)(a) GDPR. You may revoke your consent at any time with future effect. An informal email making this request is sufficient. The data processed before we receive your request may still be legally processed.We will continue to store the data collected during registration for as long as you remain registered on our website. Statutory retention periods remain unaffected.Registration with Facebook ConnectInstead of registering directly on our website, you may also register using Facebook Connect. This service is provided by Facebook Ireland Limited, 4 Grand Canal Square, Dublin 2, Ireland.If you decide to register with Facebook Connect, you will be automatically redirected to the Facebook platform. There you can log in with your Facebook username and password. This will link your Facebook profile to our website or services. This link gives us access to your data stored on Facebook. Including especially your: Facebook name Facebook profile picture Email address provided to Facebook Facebook ID Birthday Gender Country This data will be used to set up, provide, and personalize your account.For more information, see Facebook's Terms of Use and Privacy Policy. These can be found at https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/ and https://www.facebook.com/legal/terms/.Registration with Google+Instead of registering directly on our website, you may also register using Google+. This service is provided by Google LLC, 1600 Amphitheatre Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94043, USA.If you decide to register with Google+, you will be automatically redirected to the Google+ platform. There you can log in with your Google+ username and password. This will link your Google+ profile to our website or services. This link gives us access to your data stored on Google+. Including especially your: Google+ name Google+ profile picture Google+ cover picture Email address provided to Google+ Google+ ID Birthday Gender Country This data will be used to set up, provide, and personalize your account.For more information, see Google's Terms of Use and Privacy Policy. These can be found at https://policies.google.com/terms, https://www.google.com/+/policy/pagesterms.html and https://policies.google.com/privacy.Registration with TwitterInstead of registering directly on our website, you may also register using Twitter. This service is provided by Twitter Inc., 1355 Market Street, Suite 900, San Francisco, CA 94103, USA.If you decide to register with Twitter, you will be automatically redirected to the Twitter platform. There you can log in with your Twitter username and password. This will link your Twitter profile to our website or services. This link gives us access to your data stored on Twitter. Including especially your: Twitter name Twitter profile picture Twitter cover picture Email address provided to Twitter Twitter ID Birthday Gender Country This data will be used to set up, provide, and personalize your account.For more information, see Twitter's Terms of Use and Privacy Policy. These can be found at https://twitter.com/tos and https://twitter.com/privacy.Registration with GitHubInstead of registering directly on our website, you may also register using GitHub. This service is provided by GitHub, Inc, 88 Colin P Kelly Jr St, San Francisco, CA 94107, USA.If you decide to register with GitHub, you will be automatically redirected to the GitHub platform. There you can log in with your GitHub username and password. This will link your GitHub profile to our website or services. This link gives us access to your data stored on GitHub. Including especially your: GitHub name GitHub profile picture GitHub cover picture Email address provided to GitHub GitHub ID Birthday Gender Country This data will be used to set up, provide, and personalize your account.For more information, see GitHub's Terms of Use and Privacy Policy. These can be found at https://help.github.com/articles/github-terms-of-service/ and https://help.github.com/articles/github-privacy-statement/.Processing of data (customer and contract data)We collect, process, and use personal data only insofar as it is necessary to establish, or modify legal relationships with us (master data). This is done based on Art. 6 (1) (b) GDPR, which allows the processing of data to fulfill a contract or for measures preliminary to a contract. We collect, process and use your personal data when accessing our website (usage data) only to the extent required to enable you to access our service or to bill you for the same.Collected customer data shall be deleted after completion of the order or termination of the business relationship. Legal retention periods remain unaffected.Data transferred when signing up for services and digital contentWe transmit personally identifiable data to third parties only to the extent required to fulfill the terms of your contract with us, for example, to banks entrusted to process your payments.Your data will not be transmitted for any other purpose unless you have given your express permission to do so. Your data will not be disclosed to third parties for advertising purposes without your express consent.The basis for data processing is Art. 6 (1) (b) GDPR, which allows the processing of data to fulfill a contract or for measures preliminary to a contract.4. Analytics and advertising
Google reCAPTCHAWe use "Google reCAPTCHA" (hereinafter "reCAPTCHA") on our websites. This service is provided by Google Inc., 1600 Amphitheater Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94043, USA ("Google").reCAPTCHA is used to check whether the data entered on our website (such as on a contact form) has been entered by a human or by an automated program. To do this, reCAPTCHA analyzes the behavior of the website visitor based on various characteristics. This analysis starts automatically as soon as the website visitor enters the website. For the analysis, reCAPTCHA evaluates various information (e.g. IP address, how long the visitor has been on the website, or mouse movements made by the user). The data collected during the analysis will be forwarded to Google.The reCAPTCHA analyses take place completely in the background. Website visitors are not advised that such an analysis is taking place.Data processing is based on Art. 6 (1) (f) GDPR. The website operator has a legitimate interest in protecting its site from abusive automated crawling and spam.For more information about Google reCAPTCHA and Google's privacy policy, please visit the following links: https://www.google.com/intl/de/policies/privacy/ and https://www.google.com/recaptcha/intro/android.html.5. Newsletter
Newsletter dataIf you would like to receive our newsletter, we require a valid email address as well as information that allows us to verify that you are the owner of the specified email address and that you agree to receive this newsletter. No additional data is collected or is only collected on a voluntary basis. We only use this data to send the requested information and do not pass it on to third parties.We will, therefore, process any data you enter onto the contact form only with your consent per Art. 6 (1) (a) GDPR. You can revoke consent to the storage of your data and email address as well as their use for sending the newsletter at any time, e.g. through the "unsubscribe" link in the newsletter. The data processed before we receive your request may still be legally processed.The data provided when registering for the newsletter will be used to distribute the newsletter until you cancel your subscription when said data will be deleted. Data we have stored for other purposes (e.g. email addresses for the members area) remain unaffected.6. Plugins and tools
YouTubeOur website uses plugins from YouTube, which is operated by Google. The operator of the pages is YouTube LLC, 901 Cherry Ave., San Bruno, CA 94066, USA.If you visit one of our pages featuring a YouTube plugin, a connection to the YouTube servers is established. Here the YouTube server is informed about which of our pages you have visited.If you're logged in to your YouTube account, YouTube allows you to associate your browsing behavior directly with your personal profile. You can prevent this by logging out of your YouTube account.YouTube is used to help make our website appealing. This constitutes a justified interest pursuant to Art. 6 (1) (f) GDPR.Further information about handling user data, can be found in the data protection declaration of YouTube under https://www.google.de/intl/de/policies/privacy.Google Web FontsFor uniform representation of fonts, this page uses web fonts provided by Google. When you open a page, your browser loads the required web fonts into your browser cache to display texts and fonts correctly.When you call up a page of our website that contains a social plugin, your browser makes a direct connection with Google servers. Google thus becomes aware that our web page was accessed via your IP address. The use of Google Web fonts is done in the interest of a uniform and attractive presentation of our website. This constitutes a justified interest pursuant to Art. 6 (1) (f) GDPR.If your browser does not support web fonts, a standard font is used by your computer.Further information about handling user data, can be found at https://developers.google.com/fonts/faq and in Google's privacy policy at https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/.VimeoOur website uses features provided by the Vimeo video portal. This service is provided by Vimeo Inc., 555 West 18th Street, New York, New York 10011, USA.If you visit one of our pages featuring a Vimeo plugin, a connection to the Vimeo servers is established. Here the Vimeo server is informed about which of our pages you have visited. In addition, Vimeo will receive your IP address. This also applies if you are not logged in to Vimeo when you visit our website or do not have a Vimeo account. The information is transmitted to a Vimeo server in the US, where it is stored.If you are logged in to your Vimeo account, Vimeo allows you to associate your browsing behavior directly with your personal profile. You can prevent this by logging out of your Vimeo account.For more information on how to handle user data, please refer to the Vimeo Privacy Policy at https://vimeo.com/privacy.Google MapsThis site uses the Google Maps map service via an API. It is operated by Google Inc., 1600 Amphitheatre Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94043, USA.To use Google Maps, it is necessary to save your IP address. This information is generally transmitted to a Google server in the USA and stored there. The provider of this site has no influence on this data transfer.The use of Google Maps is in the interest of making our website appealing and to facilitate the location of places specified by us on the website. This constitutes a justified interest pursuant to Art. 6 (1) (f) GDPR.Further information about handling user data, can be found in the data protection declaration of Google at https://www.google.de/intl/de/policies/privacy/.SoundCloudOn our pages, plugins of the SoundCloud social network (SoundCloud Limited, Berners House, 47-48 Berners Street, London W1T 3NF, UK) may be integrated. The SoundCloud plugins can be recognized by the SoundCloud logo on our site.When you visit our site, a direct connection between your browser and the SoundCloud server is established via the plugin. This enables SoundCloud to receive information that you have visited our site from your IP address. If you click on the "Like" or "Share" buttons while you are logged into your SoundCloud account, you can link the content of our pages to your SoundCloud profile. This means that SoundCloud can associate visits to our pages with your user account. We would like to point out that, as the provider of these pages, we have no knowledge of the content of the data transmitted or how it will be used by SoundCloud. For more information on SoundCloud's privacy policy, please go to https://soundcloud.com/pages/privacy.If you do not want SoundCloud to associate your visit to our site with your SoundCloud account, please log out of your SoundCloud account.VeohOur website uses features provided by the Veoh video portal. This service is provided by FC2, 4730 South Fort Apache Road, Suite 300, Las Vegas, NV 89147, USA.If you visit one of our pages featuring a Veoh plugin, a connection to the Veoh servers is established. Here the Veoh server is informed about which of our pages you have visited. In addition, Veoh will receive your IP address. This also applies if you are not logged in to Veoh when you visit our website or do not have a Veoh account. The information is transmitted to a Veoh server in the US, where it is stored.If you are logged in to your Veoh account, Veoh allows you to associate your browsing behavior directly with your personal profile. You can prevent this by logging out of your Veoh account.For more information on how to handle user data, please refer to the Veoh Privacy Policy at http://www.veoh.com/corporate/privacypolicy.DailymotionOur website uses features provided by the Dailymotion video portal. This service is provided by Dailymotion, 140 boulevard Malesherbes, 75017 Paris, France.If you visit one of our pages featuring a Dailymotion plugin, a connection to the Dailymotion servers is established. Here the Dailymotion server is informed about which of our pages you have visited. In addition, Dailymotion will receive your IP address. This also applies if you are not logged in to Dailymotion when you visit our website or do not have a Dailymotion account.If you are logged in to your Dailymotion account, Dailymotion allows you to associate your browsing behavior directly with your personal profile. You can prevent this by logging out of your Dailymotion account.For more information on how to handle user data, please refer to the Dailymotion Privacy Policy at https://www.dailymotion.com/legal/privacy.GitHubOur website uses features provided by the GitHub. This service is provided by GitHub, Inc, 88 Colin P Kelly Jr St, San Francisco, CA 94107, USA.If you visit one of our pages featuring a GitHub plugin, a connection to the GitHub servers is established. Here the GitHub server is informed about which of our pages you have visited. In addition, GitHub will receive your IP address. This also applies if you are not logged in to GitHub when you visit our website or do not have a GitHub account. The information is transmitted to a GitHub server in the US, where it is stored.If you are logged in to your GitHub account, GitHub allows you to associate your browsing behavior directly with your personal profile. You can prevent this by logging out of your GitHub account.For more information on how to handle user data, please refer to the GitHub Privacy Policy at https://help.github.com/articles/github-privacy-statement/.SpotifyOur website uses features provided by the Spotify. This service is provided by Spotify AB, Birger Jarlsgatan 61, 113 56 Stockholm, Sweden.If you visit one of our pages featuring a Spotify plugin, a connection to the Spotify servers is established. Here the Spotify server is informed about which of our pages you have visited. In addition, Spotify will receive your IP address. This also applies if you are not logged in to Spotify when you visit our website or do not have a Spotify account.If you are logged in to your Spotify account, Spotify allows you to associate your browsing behavior directly with your personal profile. You can prevent this by logging out of your Spotify account.For more information on how to handle user data, please refer to the Spotify Privacy Policy at https://www.spotify.com/de/legal/privacy-policy/.InstagramOur website uses features provided by the Instagram. This service is provided by Instagram Inc., 1601 Willow Road, Menlo Park, CA 94025, USA.If you visit one of our pages featuring a Instagram plugin, a connection to the Instagram servers is established. Here the Instagram server is informed about which of our pages you have visited. In addition, Instagram will receive your IP address. This also applies if you are not logged in to Instagram when you visit our website or do not have a Instagram account. The information is transmitted to a Instagram server in the US, where it is stored.If you are logged in to your Instagram account, Instagram allows you to associate your browsing behavior directly with your personal profile. You can prevent this by logging out of your Instagram account.For more information on how to handle user data, please refer to the Instagram Privacy Policy at https://instagram.com/about/legal/privacy/.ImgurOur website uses features provided by the Imgur. This service is provided by Imgur, Inc., 415 Jackson Street, 2nd Floor, Suite 200, San Francisco, CA 94111, USA.If you visit one of our pages featuring a Imgur plugin, a connection to the Imgur servers is established. Here the Imgur server is informed about which of our pages you have visited. In addition, Imgur will receive your IP address. This also applies if you are not logged in to Imgur when you visit our website or do not have a Imgur account. The information is transmitted to a Imgur server in the US, where it is stored.If you are logged in to your Imgur account, Imgur allows you to associate your browsing behavior directly with your personal profile. You can prevent this by logging out of your Imgur account.For more information on how to handle user data, please refer to the Imgur Privacy Policy at https://imgur.com/privacy.TwitchOur website uses features provided by the Twitch. This service is provided by Twitch Interactive, Inc., 225 Bush Street, 6th Floor, San Francisco, CA 94104, USA.If you visit one of our pages featuring a Twitch plugin, a connection to the Twitch servers is established. Here the Twitch server is informed about which of our pages you have visited. In addition, Twitch will receive your IP address. This also applies if you are not logged in to Twitch when you visit our website or do not have a Twitch account. The information is transmitted to a Twitch server in the US, where it is stored.If you are logged in to your Twitch account, Twitch allows you to associate your browsing behavior directly with your personal profile. You can prevent this by logging out of your Twitch account.For more information on how to handle user data, please refer to the Twitch Privacy Policy at https://www.twitch.tv/p/legal/privacy-policy/.7. Payment service providers
PayPalOur website accepts payments via PayPal. The provider of this service is PayPal (Europe) S.à.r.l & Cie, S.C.A. (22-24 Boulevard Royal, L-2449 Luxembourg.If you select payment via PayPal, the payment data you provide will be supplied to PayPal based on Art. 6 (1) (a) (Consent) and Art. 6 (1) (b) GDPR (Processing for contract purposes). You have the option to revoke your consent at any time with future effect. It does not affect the processing of data previously collected.
Navigation
Dashboard
Articles
Members
Recent Activities
Users Online
Team
Search Members
(placeholder)
This site uses cookies. By continuing to browse this site, you are agreeing to our use of cookies.
More Details
Close
